

- Iserlohn, Germany
- **J** +49 (172) 393 17 67
- ≥ alexander.kondratyev.dev@gmail.com
- Shttps://alexkondratyev.github.io/linktree/
- ♦ https://t.me/kondratyev_an
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandr-kondratyev-dev/
- https://github.com/AlexKondratyev



Personal Details

Date of birth: 3 September 1994 (30 years old) in Omsk, Russia. Marital status: married, 1 kid. Nationality: Russian. From 2021 to 2023 Head of sector in Omsk Scientific-Research Institute of Instrument Engineering (JSC ONIIP). From 2019 to 2023 Junior researcher Institute of Radiophysics and Physical Electronics – subdivision of Omsk Scientific Center of the Siberian Branch of the Russian Academy of Sciences (IRPhE OSC RAS).



Education

Post-graduate student

Sept. 2018 – June 2022

Dostoevsky Omsk State University (OmSU)

Diploma thesis: Modeling of microwave communication channels based on the forecast of the state of the ionosphere.

Master of Science in Physics

Sept. 2016 - June 2018

Dostoevsky Omsk State University (OmSU)

Diploma thesis: Prediction of F2 critical frequency using statistical analysis.

Bachelor of Science in Physics

Sept. 2012 - June 2016

Dostoevsky Omsk State University (OmSU)

Diploma thesis: Research intensity distribution in the laser beam cross section.



Experiences

I have the skills to write application and embedded software. Knowledge of programming languages: C/C++ Python. Git. Knowledge of the architecture of STM32 series microcontrollers. Core: (Registers, Bus, Flash / SRAM / DRAM memories). Periphery: (GPIO, PWM, Watchdog, ADC, DMA, EEPROM, RTC). Features: (Interrupters, Timers, Counters). I used UART, SPI, I2C and 1Wire protocols in projects. Studied circuit and printed circuit board (PCB) design. Developed several electrical circuits in EasyEDA and KiCad EDA. I have ability to read documentation of various components such as (ADC, DAC, EEPROM, Operational amplifiers, etc.). Used USB protocol like CDC, DFU and HID classes in projects. Used open source file systems: FatFS, littleFS and NASA FS, in projects with a complex data storage structure. I have mentored for junior developers on one of the projects.

Head of sector Oct. 2021 - May 2023

Omsk Scientific-Research Institute of Instrument Engineering (JSC ONIIP)

Junior researcher Oct. 2019 - May 2023

Institute of Radiophysics and Physical Electronics – subdivision of Omsk Scientific Center of the Siberian Branch of the Russian Academy of Sciences (IRPhE OSC RAS)

Middle Software Engineer

Jan. 2020 - Oct. 2021

Omsk Scientific-Research Institute of Instrument Engineering (JSC ONIIP)

Junior Software Engineer

Jan. 2018 - Jan. 2020

Omsk Scientific-Research Institute of Instrument Engineering (JSC ONIIP)

Omsk Scientific-Research Institute of Instrument Engineering (JSC ONIIP)

Engineer

Oct. 2016 - Jan. 2018



Conferences, Articles & Certificates

Google Test Framework